<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on ZeaLoVe's Blogs</title><link>https://zealove.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on ZeaLoVe's Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:55 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zealove.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My view about X-ops</title><link>https://zealove.github.io/posts/xxxops/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://zealove.github.io/posts/xxxops/</guid><description>Crossing boundaries always has a magical charm, and many scientific breakthroughs are done at the intersection of disciplines.
When we go too long in a direction or methodology to find the way, perhaps a change of direction to find the intersection is a good choice.
Another example is Masayoshi Son&amp;rsquo;s approach to thinking about patents by randomly fishing for a few words from the dictionary to arrange combinations, which has to be admired.</description></item><item><title>How to Setup Blog</title><link>https://zealove.github.io/posts/how-to-setup-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 15:18:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://zealove.github.io/posts/how-to-setup-blog/</guid><description>I choose to use hugo and github page for blog hosting, before that I also tried to self-hosted way, during the university I also posted on some hosting sites such as https://www.iteye.com/blog/user/zealove.
The basic process can be done from these two introductory articles, through github action can achieve the whole automatic release, very convenient.
https://gohugo.io/getting-started/quick-start/ https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/ Cautions in addition to the edit branch, select a release branch, the default is gh-pages, hugo build directory will be committed to the release branch of things the secret GITHUB_TOKEN in the action file, do not change it, newbies like me may think to add their own token, but in fact do not need</description></item><item><title>Just begin to post something</title><link>https://zealove.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 15:44:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://zealove.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Reason Busy work always let me find my own excuses to be lazy, so many years in the notebook pile of things gradually become junk documents, and occasionally turn to only find that I have done these things.
Still not why, I just hope I can develop to organize the work content, will have done something as automated and reproducible. Otherwise, every time you encounter similar work again to ctrl-c, ctrl-v.</description></item></channel></rss>